Music from the Bob Hope Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
Guides to Special Collections in the Music Division of the Library of Congress
Music from the Bob Hope Collection 1932-1997 (bulk 1979-1990)
ML31.H67
Hope, Bob, 1903-2003
15,000 items 122 containers 35.0 linear feet
Music Division Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
In a career that spanned nearly seventy years, American comedian and entertainer Bob Hope performed in theater, radio, film, and television, and in numerous public appearances, including his tours in support of the U.S. armed forces. Music from the Bob Hope Collection contains manuscript scores, instrumental parts, and lyrics for nearly 500 works used in Hope's films, television programs and personal appearances. These materials are part of the Bob Hope collection (unprocessed), which is held by the Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division of the Library of Congress.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
People
Alberti, Bob, pianist.; Comstock, Frank.; Harmon, Manny.; Hill, J. (James L.), 1928-; Hope, Bob, 1903-2003.; Hope, Bob, 1903-2003.; Myers, Pete.; Perito, Nick.; Rogers, Shorty, 1924-1994.; Wolpe, Dave.
Organizations
Hope (Bob) Collection (Library of Congress)
Subjects
Motion picture music, Arranged.; Motion picture music--Scores.; Music--Manuscripts--United States.; Popular instrumental music.; Popular music--Lead sheets.; Popular music--United States.; Songs--Texts.; Television music, Arranged.; Television music--Scores.
Administrative Information
Provenance
Transferred from the Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, 2002-2010.
Accruals
No further music accruals are expected.
Related Material
The Library of Congress Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division holds the bulk of the Bob Hope Collection. These materials, most of which are not processed, include sound recordings and moving images, a selection of which have been cataloged and can be found in the Library of Congress online catalog where they are identified as part of the "Hope (Bob) Collection (Library of Congress)." In addition, the collection contains correspondence, photographs, scripts, notes, scrapbooks, clippings, realia, and other materials. For information about the manuscript material and sound recordings, contact a reference librarian in the Recorded Sound Reference Center. For information about the film and television materials, contact a reference librarian in the Motion Picture and Television Reading Room.
Access and Restrictions
Music from the Bob Hope Collection is open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Music Division prior to visiting in order to determine whether the desired materials will be available at that time.
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Online Content
Portions of the Bob Hope Collection have been digitized and are available in the Library of Congress online exhibitions Bob Hope and American Variety and Hope for America: Performers, Politics and Pop Culture.
Biographical Note
Biographical information on Bob Hope is available in the Library of Congress online exhibition Bob Hope and American Variety.
Scope and Content Note
Music from the Bob Hope Collection consists of manuscript and photocopied full scores, conductor's scores, parts, lead sheets, and lyric sheets for nearly 500 titles used in Hope's films, television programs and personal appearances. Many of the arrangements were written for short play-on and play-offs, interludes, and cues for Hope's television specials and USO tour appearances. The collection also includes fully arranged songs written for solo or duet performances by notable guests on the Bob Hope Show. Most of the arrangements were written by Bob Alberti, Nick Perito and J. Hill. Additional arrangers represented in the collection include Frank Comstock, Manny Harmon, Pete Myers, Shorty Rogers and Dave Wolpe. The first series, Music from Identified Films, Television Programs and Public Appearances, contains works identified from information included on the music or original accompanying folders. The series is arranged chronologically by date of film, television program or event. Individual songs are listed therein. The second series, Music from Unidentified Sources, contains works whose sources were not able to be identified. This series is arranged alphabetically by work title. Qualifying information (e.g. "play-on") and date of the arrangement are provided wherever possible.
Organization of Music from the Bob Hope Collection
Music from the Bob Hope Collection is organized in two series:
Music from Identified Films, Television Programs and Public Appearances, 1953-1997
Music from Unidentified Sources, 1932-1992
http://lccn.loc.gov/2006560672
Container List
- Music from Identified Films, Television Programs and Public Appearances, 1953-1997 (Box 1-54, 82-90, 95-112, 117-121)
  Manuscript scores, parts, lead sheets, and lyric sheets for works from identified films, television programs, and public appearances. Lists of titles are provided when there is corresponding music. Part sets are assumed to be complete unless otherwise noted.
  Arranged chronologically by date of film, television program, or event.
  - 1953: Off limits (film), Scores and parts; Titles: All about love (Marilyn Maxwell, Bob Hope) (Box-folder 1/1)
  - 1953 December 15: The Bob Hope TV Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Silver bells (Box-folder 1/2)
  - 1955: The seven little foys (film), Bound libretto/music score; Inscribed: Dear Bob, A merry, merry Christmas! from Joseph J. Lilley, 1954 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - 1958: Paris holiday (film), Scores, parts, lyric sheets; Titles: Nothing in common; Paris holiday; miscellaneous cues; Ursula's theme (Box-folder 2/1-7; 3/1-9; 4/1-5; 5/1-9; 82/1-3)
  - 1959 May 15: The Bob Hope show, Scores, parts, lyric sheets; Titles: Ain't a-hankerin' (Rosemary Clooney) (Box-folder 6/1)
  - 1961: Bachelor in paradise (movie theme), Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/2)
  - 1964 December 13: Bob Hope Christmas in Vinh Long, Vietnam, Scores and parts; Titles: Flattery (Janis Paige) (Box-folder 6/3)
  - 1967 (air date, 1968 January 18): The Bob Hope Vietnam Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Buckle down, Winsocki; Football playoff - Winsocki; The most beautiful girl; Prisoner of love (Box-folder 6/4-7)
  - 1970: The Bob Hope benefit for the Eisenhower Medical Center, Scores and parts; Titles: Hope/Crosby medley; Put it there, pal (Box-folder 7/1-2)
  - 1971 January 14: The Bob Hope Vietnam Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Fly me to the moon (Alan Shepard); Silver bells (Box-folder 8/1-2)
  - 1971 November 7: The Bob Hope special, Scores and parts; Titles: America play-off (John Wayne) (Box-folder 8/3)
  - 1972 February 27: Bing Crosby and friends (NBC), Scores and parts; Titles: Saturday morning confusion (Box-folder 8/4; 9/1; 122/1)
  - 1975 October: A quarter century of Bob Hope on television, Scores and parts; Titles: Crosby (play-on) (Box-folder 82/4)
  - 1975 December: Bob Hope Christmas, Scores and parts; Titles: Thanks for the memories (Box-folder 82/5)
  - 1976 June ?: Bob Hope TV, Scores and parts; Titles: Hartford (play-on/off) (Box-folder 82/6)
  - 1976 December 12: The Bob Hope comedy Christmas special, Scores and parts; Titles: Christmas medley (Lola Falana); Go-go dance; Jingle bells (segue); Thanks / Christmas; Toyland ethereal; We wish you a merry Christmas (play-off) (Box-folder 9/2; 82/7-9)
  - 1977 January 21: Bob Hope's all-star comedy spectacular from Lake Tahoe, Scores and parts; Titles: Lullaby to King King; One; Rocky theme; Tahoe cues (Box-folder 9/3-4; 10/1-2)
  - 1977 March 25: Bob Hope's all-star comedy tribute to Vaudeville, Scores and parts; Titles: Button up your overcoat; Camelot fanfare; The curtain falls; Harlem nocturne; I know that you know; King Arthur's Court; Love nest; Love will keep us together; Salute to Sophie (Lucille Ball); Thanks for the memories; There's no business like show business (underscore); Vaudeville come-on; Vaudeville ladies; We're in the money (Box-folder 10/3-8; 83/1-6; 95/1-2)
  - 1977 December 19: Bob Hope's all-star Christmas comedy special, Scores and parts, sheet music; Titles: Luke Skywalker; Muppets movie; Scar wars: Silver bells '77 (Box-folder 84/1-4)
  - 1978 February 13: The Bob Hope special from Palm Springs, Scores and parts; Titles: Stayin' alive (Box-folder 11/1)
  - 1978 April 15: Bob Hope's all-star comedy special from Australia, Scores and parts; Titles: Cruising down the river; Koala kaper; Waltzing Matilda; Tie me kangaroo down, sport; What would I do without my music? (Kamahl) (Box-folder 11/2; 85/1-3; 95/3)
  - 1978 October 18: Bob Hope's salute to the 75th anniversary of the World Series, Scores and parts; Titles: Ball game swing; Baseball around the World; Baseball number; Moider the ump!; Take me out to the ballgame (Box-folder 95/4-5; 96/1-2)
  - 1978 December 3: Bob Hope's salute to Ohio theater, Scores and parts; Titles: Happiness boys (with Vic Damone); Jingle bells; Thanks for the memories (Box-folder 11/3; 85/4-5)
  - 1978 December 22: The Bob Hope Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Jingle bells; Silent night; Silver bells (underscore) (Box-folder 11/4-6)
  - 1979 January 28: The Bob Hope cavalcade of comedy special, Scores and parts; Titles: H-O-P-E opening; To be a performer (Box-folder 86/1-2)
  - 1979 May 30: Bob Hope's birthday party at sea (U.S.S. Iwo Jima, N.Y.C. Harbour), Scores and parts; Titles: Another opening; Good sports; I don't need anything but you (Sara Jessica Parker); New York medley (Diahann Carroll) (Box-folder 12/1-2; 86/3-4)
  - 1979 September 16: Bob Hope on the road to China, Scores and parts; Titles: Acrobat hoopla; Acrobats; Big Bird walk; Circus floppus; Colgate fight song; Do-re-mi; Golf stroke; Great wall (opening); I left my heart in San Francisco (parody); If my friends could see me now; New York medley (revised); Peking Hotel; Ping pong song; Road to China; T'ai chee; Tea for two; Tien-a-men square; Together, wherever we go; When I was a lad (Box-folder 12/3; 13/1-6; 86/5-6; 97/1-4; 98/1-4; 122/3)
  - 1979 November 19: Hope on campus, Scores and parts; Titles: Alabama victory; Colgate fight song; Florida University; Harvard; Indiana fight song (Box-folder 14/1-5; 86/7)
  - 1980 January 21: Bob Hope special: Hope, women, and song, Scores and parts; Titles: Buttons and bows; Don't bring Lulu; Down in the depths; It's delovely; The lady's in love with you; miscellaneous scores; Nobody; Opening billboard; Thanks for the memories; Two sleepy people (Shirley Jones) (Box-folder 14/6; 15/1-3; 16/1-5; 99/1-3)
  - 1980 February 3 and 10: Bob Hope's overseas Christmas tours: around the world with the troops, 1941-1972, Scores and parts; Titles: show 2: cues, scores, invoices for arrangements (Box-folder 17; 99/4)
  - 1980 May 28: Bob Hope Air Force Academy special, Scores and parts; Titles: Flying medley; Reach out and touch (Diana Ross) (Box-folder 18/1-2)
  - 1980 September 6: Bob Hope's look at the new TV season, Scores and parts; Titles: The Carioca; The Continental; Everything happens to us; How are things in Glocca Morra (parody); Isle of Capri; Love boat theme; Moon over Miami; Tomorrow (Box-folder 18/3-6; 87/1-2; 117/1-4)
  - 1980 November 1: Bob Hope for president, Scores and parts; Titles: Hail to Hope; Hail to the Hope-ful; Hope for America; Hope for president (end credits);miscellaneous cues; miscellaneous scores; A real song and dance man (with Sammy Davis Jr.); Thanks for the memories (Box-folder 19/1-4; 87/3-4; 99/5; 117/5)
  - 1980 December 16: Bob Hope Christmas show and all-star comedy special, Scores and parts; Titles: Joy to the world (Box-folder 87/5)
  - 1981 January 18: The Bob Hope 30th anniversary TV special, Scores and parts; Titles: Shogun; Take this job and shove it; Thirty years of Hope (show theme) (Box-folder 19/5; 100/1-2)
  - 1981 February 11: Bob Hope's funny valentine special, Scores and parts; Titles: Fort Worth; Valentine medley (Box-folder 20/1)
  - 1981 April 13: Bob Hope's spring fling of glamour and comedy, Scores and parts; Titles: The girl next door (Melissa Manchester) (Box-folder 100/3)
  - 1981 May 25: Bob Hope at West Point, Scores and parts; Titles: 45 minutes from Broadway; Happy/sad medley; Honey bun; Hum-bug; Rhinestone cowboy (Box-folder 21/1-3; 101/1-2)
  - 1981 September 27: Bob Hope's all-star comedy look at the fall season: it's still free and worth it!, Scores and parts; Titles: Barney Miller theme; Dukes of Hazzard; M.A.S.H.; (Box-folder 101/3; 102/1-2)
  - 1981 October 22: Bob Hope's all-star celebration opening the Gerald R. Ford Presidential Museum, Scores and parts; Titles: Four of a kind; Once in love with Betty (Box-folder 22/1-2)
  - 1981 November 22: Bob Hope's stand up and cheer for the National Football League's sixtieth year, Scores and parts; Titles: All-American wreck; Hot lunch jam; Nine to five (lineman's lament); When Winter comes; You don't have to know the language (Box-folder 23/1-5)
  - 1981 December 20: The Bob Hope Christmas special, Scores and parts; Titles: Happy holidays; Me and my shadow; Silver bells; Small fry (Box-folder 24/1-4)
  - 1982 February 28: Bob Hope's women I love: beautiful but funny, Scores and parts; Titles: How to handle a woman; Thanks for the memories (dame opening) (Box-folder 25/1-2)
  - 1982 May 3: Bob Hope's stars over Texas special, Scores and parts; Titles: Anyone who isn't me (Dottie West); Caddy; Doorbells; The eyes of Texas; Golf stroke; Texas golf (Box-folder 25/3-6; 26/1; 102/3)
  - 1982 May 25: Bob Hope's all-star birthday party in Annapolis, Scores and parts; Titles: Air Force theme; Anchors aweigh; Naval medley (Box-folder 26/2-4)
  - 1982 October 3: Bob Hope's star-studded spoof of the new TV season: G-rated, with glamour, glitter and gags, Scores and parts; Titles: Crappy days; General horse-pistol (Box-folder 27/1-2)
  - 1982 November 21: Bob Hope's Pink Panther Thanksgiving special, Scores and parts; Titles: Getting to know you (play-on); Lady spies; Thanks for the memories (opening); Waiting in the wings (Box-folder 27/3-5; 102/4)
  - 1983 January 29: Bob Hope's all-star Superbowl party, Scores and parts; Titles: Football hero; Love is in the air; Shirley Temple medley; The strapper (Don Rickles); Superbowl opening (Box-folder 28/1-5)
  - 1983 March 2: Bob Hope's road to Hollywood, Scores and parts; Titles: Guzzle; Hooray to Hollywood (play-on, play-off); Road to Hollywood; Shower intruder (William Bendix) (Box-folder 29/1-4)
  - 1983 April 20: Bob Hope in Who makes the world laugh?, Scores and parts; Titles: The Twain never meets (Box-folder 29/5)
  - 1983 May 23: Happy birthday, Bob!: Kennedy Center Tribute, Scores and parts; Titles: Arthur (play on); Fashion show; Gym dance; Hey, look me over; Hey, look me over (transposed, key of G); Just the way you are; Kermit (play-on); Love is the foundation; Magnum P.I.; Secret love; You made me love you; You must have been a beautiful baby (Box-folder 29/6-7; 30/1-5; 31/1-2; 87/6-7; 122/4)
  - 1983 September 19: Bob Hope's salute to NASA: 25 years of reaching for the stars, Scores and parts; Titles: Flight (John Denver); Floating in space; Moon medley; Road to Morocco (parody with Perry Como) (Box-folder 31/3-6)
  - 1983 November 23: Bob Hope goes to college, Scores and parts; Titles: Clemson: Tiger rag; Notre Dame: Victory march; S.M.U. Peruna; Syracuse: Down the field; UCLA: Sons of Westwood; Utah State: Aggies all the way (Box-folder 32/1-2; 87/8-11; 103/1)
  - 1983 December 19: Bob Hope's merry Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Cabbage-patch dolls; Christmas cues; You're all I want for Christmas (Box-folder 32/3-4)
  - 1984 January 15: The Bob Hope U.S.O. Christmas in Beirut, Scores and parts; Titles: I've got a crush on you; Standin' on the corner; The two of us (Ann Jillian); We love working together (Brooke Shields) (Box-folder 32/5-6; 33/1-2)
  - 1984 February 27: Bob Hope's wicki-wacky special from Waikiki, Scores and parts; Titles: Aloha, oe; Hawaii; Hawaii Five-O; Hawaii opening; It's a lovely day today (Loni Anderson); Little grass shack; Lovely hula hands; Thanks for the memories; Would you like to take a walk? (Box-folder 33/3-6; 34/1-5)
  - 1984 April 4: Bob Hope in Who makes the world laugh? Part 2, Scores and parts; Titles: Tea for two (Box-folder 35/1)
  - 1984 May 28: Bob Hope's super birthday special at the World's Fair, New Orleans, Scores and parts; Titles: A-team; David Letterman (play-on, play-off); Flying medley; How long has this been going on? (Twiggy); I can't get started with you; Johnny Cash (play on); Make believe; Riverboat ramble; Road to New Orleans; Way down yonder in New Orleans (Box-folder 35/2-4; 36/1-6; 87/12)
  - 1984 May 31: The Criss awards, Scores and parts; Titles: Globelus (play-on) (George Gobel); Wild Kingdom (play-on) (Box-folder 37/1-2)
  - 1984 December 16: The Bob Hope show: it's a ho ho Hope's jolly Christmas hour, Scores and parts; Titles: Anything you can do (Mary Lou Retton); Give my regards to Broadway (Joey Lawrence); Tea for two (Box-folder 37/3-4; 103/2)
  - 1985 February: Bob Hope show, Scores and parts; Titles: We're hucksters (Box-folder 37/5)
  - 1985 April 15: Bob Hope show: comedy salute to the soaps, Scores and parts; Titles: I never miss my soaps (Diahann Carroll) (Box-folder 38/1)
  - 1985 May 28: Bob Hope happy birthday homecoming (London Royal Gala), Scores and parts; Titles: Gandhi (Ben Kingsley); London medley; Rule Brittania (Box-folder 39/1-3)
  - 1985 September 17: Bob Hope buys NBC?, Scores and parts; Titles: Buy bonds for Bob; God save NBC; Young-smoothie medley (Box-folder 39/4-6)
  - 1985: The Bob Hope Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Sad jingle bells (play on); Side by side; (Box-folder 40/1-2)
  - 1986 January: The Bob Hope Superbowl party, Scores and parts; Titles: Football widow; N.F.L. clips medley (Box-folder 40/3; 41/1)
  - 1986 March: Bob Hope's royal command performance from Sweden, Scores and parts; Titles: Cold medley (Shirley Jones); Over the rainbow; Sunny side of the street; Tumbling tumbleweeds (Glen Campbell) (Box-folder 41/2-4; 42/1)
  - 1986 May: Bob Hope's high-flying birthday party (aboard the U.S.S. Lexington), Scores and parts; Titles: I can do that (Sammy Davis Jr.) (Box-folder 88/1)
  - 1986 September 15: Bob Hope's new TV season, Scores and parts; Titles: The media; Moonlighting (Box-folder 42/2-3)
  - 1986 November: Bob Hope's tropical comedy special from Tahiti, Scores and parts; Titles: Tahiti medley (Box-folder 42/4)
  - 1986 December: Bob Hope Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Music hall; Rocka-Getty Christmas (Box-folder 103/3-4)
  - 1987 April 19: The Bob Hope show: Easter bunnies and friends, Scores and parts; Titles: Easter medley; Peter Cottontail (play-on) (Box-folder 44/3; 104/1)
  - 1987 May: Bob Hope's high-flying birthday at Pope Air Force Base, Scores and parts; Titles: Carolina in the morning; Flight (Glen Campbell); I remember it well; Lucy theme; Whirling spinners; Wings; Wings 2; Wings 3 (Box-folder 43/1-5; 44/1-2)
  - 1987 September: The Bob Hope show, Scores and parts; Titles: A man is innocent (Box-folder 44/4)
  - 1987 December: The Bob Hope Winterfest Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Appalachicola (Tony Randall) (Box-folder 45/1; 88/2)
  - 1988 January 8: Bob Hope's U.S.O. Christmas from the Persian Gulf: around the world in eight days, Scores and parts; Titles: One (Box-folder 45/2)
  - 1988 May: The Bob Hope 85th birthday show / 50 years with NBC, Scores and parts; Titles: Comedy ain't no joke; Comedy (play-off and reprise); Doin' the Bob Hope show; Lucy (comedy play-off); Oscar and me; Personality; Sentimental 976; Travelin' man; Vaudeville; You're invited to a party (Box-folder 46/1-4; 47/1-4; 48/1-2)
  - 1988 September: HNN Hope News Network, Scores and parts; Titles: That's the news (Box-folder 49/1)
  - 1988: Bob Hope’s royal Viking Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Christmas bridge; It's not where you start; (Box-folder 49/2-4)
  - 1989: Bob Hope’s Easter vacation in the Bahamas, Scores and parts; Titles: Customs sktech (play on) (Box-folder 50/1)
  - 1989: Ooh-la-la: it's Bob Hope's fun birthday spectacular from Paris, Scores and parts; Titles: American in Paris; C'est magnifique; I love Paris; I'm glad I'm not young anymore; Love is here to stay; Thank Heaven for little girls (Louis Jourdan); Thanks for the memories/French closing; Valse du Paree (Box-folder 50/2-7; 51/1-2)
  - 1990 February 17: Bob Hope spoofs show business, Scores and parts; Titles: Should we go see a movie? (Box-folder 51/3)
  - 1990 April: Bob Hope’s spring in Acapulco, Scores and parts; Titles: Acapulco (play-off); One hot tamale; They say it's wonderful (Ann Jillian) (Box-folder 52/1-3)
  - 1990 May 19: Bob Hope’s U.S.O. road to the Berlin Wall and Moscow, Scores and parts; Titles: Old friends; Russian fly over (Box-folder 52/4; 88/3)
  - 1990 September 15: Bob Hope’s Don't shoot, it's only me, Scores and parts; Titles: I could write a book; Queen Miltie's tango; Uncle Milltown (Box-folder 52/5-7)
  - 1990: Bob Hope's 1990 Christmas show from Bermuda, Scores and parts; Titles: Christmas medley; White Christmas (Box-folder 53/1-2)
  - 1991: Bob Hope and friends: making new memories, Scores and parts; Titles: Voices that care; Well, did you evah? (Box-folder 53/3-4)
  - 1991: The Bob Hope Christmas show, Scores and parts; Titles: Jingle bells (underscore); Joy to the world (play-off); Silver snowflakes (Box-folder 54/1-3)
  - 1992 May 16: Bob Hope’s America: red, white and blue – the swimsuit edition, Scores and parts; Titles: Alexander's ragtime band (Box-folder 54/4)
  - 1992 December 19: Bob Hope’s Christmas show (San Antonio, Texas), Scores and parts; Titles: Silver bells "mariachi" (Box-folder 88/4)
  - 1993 May 14: Bob Hope: The first 90 years, Scores and parts; Titles: Always; America the beautiful; Bob's soft shoe; Boogie woogie bugle boy; Bumpers 1-6 (with lyric sheets); Buttons and bows; Cagney/Hope 3; Christmas cues; Color Guard medley; Come fly with me; Fanfare; Dance intro; Dancer's playoff; Fine and dandy; Happy birthday; I can't get started with you/Delovely; I'll be home for Christmas (Ann Jillian); The lady's in love; Love nest (George Burns play-on); Moon of Manakoora; Opening 1; Opening (2-6); Radio: In the mood; Roseanne theme song; Silver bells; Thanks for the memories; Vaudeville (Box-folder 54/5-6; 88/5-6; 104/2-4; 105-109)
  - 1993 December: A Bob Hope Christmas, Scores and parts; Titles: Christmas cues; Christmas opening; Christmas party medley; Dolores Christmas medley (oversize); Football medley; I wish it could be Christmas forever; Mr. Touchdown USA; Rah-rah cheerleaders (Box-folder 54/7; 89/1; 110; 118/1-2)
  - 1994 May 14: Happy 91st birthday, Bob, Scores and parts; Titles: Boxing (dream cues); Coffee for one; Everything's coming up roses; Happy birthday (soft shoe); Happy Hope day; High flying Hope; How high the moon; I can do that (score in May 1986 birthday folder); I can't get started; Kissing; Peter Gunn (paraphrase); Rocky (Box-folder 54/8-9; 89/2-4; 111; 112/1-4)
  - 1994 June: Bob Hope in England, Scores and parts; Titles: Hope play-off; Memories (Box-folder 54/10)
  - 1994 December: Bob Hope's Christmas show: Hopes for the holidays, Scores and parts; Titles: Christmas opening; Do you hear what I hear?; Happy holiday/let's have a party (Box-folder 54/11; 89/5; 112/5; 119/1)